Yisak Wondim

0947728633 | it.yisak.wondim@gmail.com | Woreda 04 Kolfe Keranio, Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa

Summary

A proactive IT officer at Orbis Trading and Technical center. I have great expertise on computer hardware and software installation and maintenance, networking and database administration with good English and Amharic proficiency, both writing and speaking. My High affinity towards ICT related topics makes me preferred for IT tasks.

Experience

Orbis Trading and Technical center | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa IT officer | 09/2022 - Present

- · Desktop support
- · Network configuration and maintenance
- Web development

Tensae Internet Cafe | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa IT Technician | 02/2021 - 11/2021

- · Configuring computer Hardware and Software
- · Managing time and price tracking software
- · Configuring and managing network

Addis Ababa Institute of Technology | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Software Developer Intern | 03/2020 - 09/2020

- · Software Documentation Control
- API Design and Development
- · Database Design

Skills

Vmware, VPN, Linux

Education

Addis Ababa University | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Information Technology | 07/2022 GPA:3.35